### Nicolas Santiago Del Vecchio

Morón-Buenos Aires, Argentina nnicou.s@gmail.com +54 11 7364-2629 <u>LinkedIn nicolas-del-vecchio</u> <u>GitHub Caapu-nico</u>

Full Stack Developer with a background in selling technological solutions, which has allowed me to have a complete vision of the business. Knowledge of backend and frontend technologies including JavaScript, SQL, Sequelize, Express, MongoDb, Postgress, Node.js, React, and Redux. With an excellent predisposition for teamwork, dynamism, capacity for continuous learning and enthusiasm. I have worked on individual and group projects with agile methodologies. Always willing to continue acquiring knowledge in technology. B1 intermediate level of English.

# **Technologies**

Programming languages: JavaScript.

Framework tools: Express.js, Node.js, Sequelize, Mongoose, React-Redux.

**Database:** SQL, Postgress, MongoDb. **Tools:** Git, Jira, Confluence, Slack.

Agile: Scrum.

#### **Projects**

Full Stack Web Developer - Project Notices

January 2023

- 1. Development of a news website, only visual and aesthetic.
- 2. Implementation of functionalities such as dynamic navbar management, detailed cards, background and footer.
- 3. Use of cloudflare, Font Google, Font gstatic, CSS y HTML.

Full Stack Web Developer - Individual Project Countries Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Agosto 2023

- 4. Development of an application in order to display country cards with their capitals, population, continents, flags and activities.
- 5. Implementation of functionalities such as alphabetical ordering of countries, region, tourist activity and number of inhabitants. Search by name and activity and create new activities.

1. Use of technologies such as JavaScript, React, Redux, Express, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, CSS, and HTML.

Back End Developer - Final Project "ProjUnity" Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

*Sep-Oct* 2023

- 2. Development of an e-commerce platform for freelance developers where they can interact with users, share their code, sell it, donate it and contribute to the community.
- 3. Integration of shopping carts, purchase orders, authentication of both new and third-party users, notifications, registration of comments, creation of new projects and management of orders.
- 4. Key contribution in the development of the server/database with the assembly of routes, assembly of models, payment market, payments and purchase orders, user comments, creation of projects and deployment of the database.
- 5. Use of technologies such as JavaScript, React-Redux, Next.js, Express, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, CSS, ChakraUI, and HTML. Use of Cloudinary, MercadoPago, Passport, Railway and Vercel.

"ProjUnity"

### **Academic Experience**

Full Stack Developer Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina. January/2023-Present

- 1. Compliance with the schedule of assigned projects, homeworks, checkpoints, classes and detailed documentation.
- 2. Language: Proficiency in JavaScript and ECMAScript 2015 for the development of efficient and interactive web applications.
- 3. Frontend: Manipulating the DOM and using CSS to create attractive and responsive interfaces.
- 4. Backend: Implement an application's server development, logic, and functionality, ensuring efficient performance and robust data management. Ensuring accurate and concrete answers from the server.
- 5. Frameworks: In the development of the implensed frontend as I use React-Redux. From the backend side, we use Node.js as a runtime environment and Express as a framework, handling good modularization and effective code reading.
- 6. Database: Handling Sequelize as an ORM for efficient queries and interactions using JavaScript-to-database (SQL) functions with model and relationship handling.
- Testing: Ability to perform unit testing, troubleshooting, reading, and respective use of the documentation.

#### **Professional Education**

Full Stack Developer - Henry Bootcamp / December 2023 - Present.

Bachelor's Degree in Economic Sciences-Instituto fragata Sarmiento E.S.A n 9 / December 2019.

\_\_\_\_\_

## **Supplementary Education**

Italian course level B1 module 1° - New Knowledge Academy / February 2023 - Present.

Bartending Course - I.G.A Instituto Gastronómico de Argentina / October 2017.

## Work experience

**Telephone Operator – Cat Technologies**/ February 2023 - Present.

Sales and customer service for Telecom company. Management of SalesForce, Open and Siebel CRM in internet, cable and mobile sales management. Invoicing and administrative procedures.

Bartender – ShawarmaBar/ The Mansion / Pizza Warehouse / March 2022 – December 2022

Bar manager and bar assistant for different branches and restaurants, stock control, good disposition with the customer, creation of house and signature drinks. "Received as a professional bartender at I.G.A Instituto Gastronómico Argentino"

#### **Languages**

**ENGLISH B1 INTERMEDIATE to B2 UPPER INTERMEDIATE**, in accordance with the guidelines set by the Common European Framework of Reference (CEFR).

**BASIC ITALIAN** (in process)

**NATIVE SPANISH**